<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalExerciseApplication</string>
    <string name="shannon_sosebee">Shannon Sosbee</string>
    <string name="anthony_woodall">Anthony Woodall</string>
    <string name="ethan_tinsley">Ethan Tinsley</string>

    Strings used in main activity
    <string name="MainPageTitle">Emergence Fitness! </string>
    <string name="StartWorkoutButton">Start Workout!</string>
    <string name="BuildWorkoutButton">Build a Workout!</string>
    <string name="ViewExistingWorkouts">View Existing Workouts!</string>
    <string name="PreviousWorkoutsButton">Previous Workouts</string>
    <string name="BrowseExercisesButton">Browse Available Exercises!</string>

    strings used in build workout activity
    <string name="BuildExerciseTitle">Build a New Workout</string>
    <string name="AddAnExercise"> Add a new Exercise to the Workout</string>
    <string name="SaveTheWorkout">Save Workout </string>
    <string name="UserInputTitle">New Workout Title: </string>

    Strings for Muscle Groups
    <string name="Shoulders">Shoulders</string>
    <string name="Bicep">Biceps</string>
    <string name="Tricep">Triceps</string>
    <string name="Forearm">Forearms</string>
    <string name="Chest">Chest</string>
    <string name="Back">Back</string>
    <string name="Abdominal">Abdominal</string>
    <string name="Glutes">Glutes</string>
    <string name="Hamstrings">Hamstrings</string>
    <string name="Calves">Calves</string>

    Strings for Chest Exercises
    <string name="BenchPress">Barbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="BenchPressDescription">The barbell bench press is an upper-body weight training exercise in which the person lays flat on their
    back on a weight training bench and pushes a barbell upwards towards the ceiling</string>

    <string name="InclineBenchPress">Incline Bench Press</string>
    <string name="InclineBenchPressDescription">The incline barbell bench press is a version of the traditional bench press in which the bench is
    positioned at about a 45 degree angle resulting in an inclined position</string>

    <string name="DeclineBenchPress">Decline Bench Press</string>
    <string name="DeclineBenchPressDescription">The decline bench press is another version of the traditional bench press in which the bench is set
    to a 15 to 30 degree decline, placing the body on a downward slope</string>

    <string name="CableFly">Cable Fly</string>
    <string name="CableFlyDescription">A cable fly is performed on a machine with cable resistance usually in the standing position. One uses both sides
    of the machine, on cable in each hand. The user pushes both arms out in front of them and then while keeping arms slightly bent, slowly releases both arms
    at the same time back towards the machine. When getting to a point that is safe for the user, they will then pull these cables back to the original start
    position in front of them, simulating a flying movement</string>

    <string name="DumbbellBenchPress">Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="DumbbellBenchPressDescription">The dumbbell bench press is an upper-body weight training exercise in which the person lays flat on their
    back on a weight training bench with a dumbbell in each hand and pushes the dumbbells upwards towards the ceiling</string>

    <string name="DeclineDumbbellBenchPress">Decline Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="DeclineDumbbellBenchPressDescription">The decline dumbbell bench press is a version of the dumbbell bench press in which the bench is set
    to a 15 to 30 degree decline, placing the body on a downward slope</string>

    <string name="InclineDumbbellBenchPress">Incline Dumbbell Bench Press</string>
    <string name="InclineDumbbellBenchPressDescription">The incline dumbbell bench press is another version of the dumbbell bench press in which the bench is
    positioned at about a 45 degree angle resulting in an inclined position</string>

    <string name="DumbbellFly">Dumbbell Fly</string>
    <string name="DumbbellFlyDescription">The dumbbell fly is a movement where the user uses two dumbbells and lies flat on their back on a bench holding the
    dumbbell directly in front of them. The user then lowers both dumbbells towards their side while keeping their arms slightly bent. After reaching a safe
    point, the user returns back to the start position and then repeats</string>

    <string name="Pushups">Pushups</string>
    <string name="PushupsDescription">The pushup is an exercise where a person lies facing the floor and, keeping their back straight, raises their body by
    pressing down on their hands, pushing themselves up from the ground</string>

    Strings for forearms

    <string name="BarbellHolds">Barbell Holds</string>
    <string name="BarbellHoldsDescription">The barbell hold is an exercise where the barbell is placed on a rack at hip level. The person then grabs the bar
    with hands just outside of thighs and lifts the bar off of the rack holding the bar up with arms hanging down in front of them</string>

    <string name="HandGripper">Hand Gripper </string>
    <string name="HandGripperDescription">The handgripper is a device that simulates a crushing movement. The person sets the resistance on the device in which
    they would like to use then grabs the device and closes their hand against the resistance</string>

    <string name="PlatePinch">Plate Pinch</string>
    <string name="PlatePinchDescription">A plate pinch is a movement a person does by grabbing a plate and picking it up using their fingers in a pinching motion
    and holding the plate off of the ground for a certain amount of time</string>

    <string name="FarmersCarries">Farmer Carries</string>
    <string name="FarmersCarriesDescription">A farmers carry involves a person holding a weight, either dumbbell or kettlebell, in each hand and walking for a
    certain distance or time</string>

    Strings for Triceps

    <string name="DumbbellTricepExtensions">Dumbbell Tricep Extensions </string>
    <string name="DumbbellTricepExtensionsDescription">To do a dumbbell tricep extension the person will start in a standing or sitting position with dumbbells
    in each hand. The person raises the dumbbells above their head with arms extended out above. The dumbbells then slowly get lowered behind the head doing
    best to not let the elbows flare out. When the forearms move slightly past parallel to the floor, bring weight back to starting position</string>

    <string name="Dips">Dips </string>
    <string name="DipsDefinition">To perform a dip, a person uses a dip attachment or the edge of a bench/chair. If using an attachment, the person will hold their
    body off of the ground and slowly lower themselves down and then after breaking the parallel point with their elbows, will push themselves back up into the
    starting position. If using a chair/bench the user will grip the bench/chair with their fingers point down towards the floor and elbows pointed behind them.
    The person will walk their feet out in front of them extending themselves out, slowly lower themselves down then pushing themselves back into the starting
    position</string>

    <string name="SeatedTricepPress">Seated Tricep Press</string>
    <string name="SeatedTricepPressDefinition">Tp perform the seated tricep extension the person will take one dumbbell at a time and get in a seated position.
    the person will then put the dumbbell up on their shoulder, flaring their elbow out to the side. Once in position, the person will extend the dumbbell up to
    the ceiling while doing best to keep elbow in the same position and then lowering the dumbbell back into the starting position</string>

    <string name="TricepCablePushdowns">Tricep Cable Pushdowns </string>
    <string name="TricepCablePushdownsDescription">The machine tricep extension is used with a rope attachment on a cable machine. The person stands in front
    of the rope and grasps with both hands. The person then lowers arms down and locks both elbows down by their side. The rope is then pushed down extending both
    arms down towards the floor flaring at the bottom and then returning to starting position, keeping both elbows stuck to the side the entire time</string>

    <string name="SkullCrushers">Skull Crushers </string>
    <string name="SkullCrushersDescription">The skullcrusher is used commonly with a preacher curl bar. The person will use this bar and lay flat on their back
    extending their arms directly above them. While keeping their elbows pinched in, the person lowers the bar down close to the bridge of the nose, hence nose
    buster, and then pushes the arms back to the original extended position</string>

    Strings for Shoulders

    <string name="SeatedOverheadWeightedPress">Seated Overhead Weighted Press</string>
    <string name="SeatedOverheadWeightedPressDescription">To perform this exercise, the person will start in a seated position with the bar racked to a similar height
    in front of them. They will grip the bar and place it on their front shoulders with hands slightly wider then their shoulders. The person will then press
    the bar over their head until the arms are fully extended and then lower the bar back to the front of the shoulders</string>

    <string name="WeightedLateralRaises">Weighted Lateral Raises </string>
    <string name="WeightedLateralRaisesDescription">The lateral raise is performed with a dumbbell in each hand with arms fully extended down by the side. The
    person will then, while keeping the arms straight and body locked into place, use their shoulder muscles to pull the dumbbells up to the ceiling at a 45 degree
    angle from directly in front of them</string>

    <string name="WeightedFrontRaises">Weighted Front Raises </string>
    <string name="WeightedFrontRaisesDescription">The front raise is similar to the lateral raise but except for the person raising the dumbbells at a 45 degree
    angle, the user lifts them directly in front of them using the front part of their shoulder to do so while keeping the body locked in place and keeping the
    arms locked out as well</string>

    <string name="WeightedUprightRows">Weighted Upright Rows</string>
    <string name="WeightedUprightRowsDescription">To perform a weighted upright row, the person will load a barbell with a safe weight and lift the barbell from the
    ground while in a standing position. The arms will be completely straightened in front of the person. The person will then pull the weight straight up, keeping
    their elbows up the entire time and flared to the side. After pulling the weight straight up as high as the persons arms will let them, they will slowly
    lower the weight back into the start position</string>

    <string name="ArnoldPress">Arnold Press </string>
    <string name="ArnoldPressDescription">To do the arnold press, the person with start by standing with dumbbells in each hand, shoulder height, with elbows bent and
    palms facing the body. The person brings the elbows out wide to the side while rotating hands so the palms face forward and pressing the dumbbells over head
    until the arms are straight out. Pause at the top, and the reverse the movement to return to the start position</string>

    <string name="WeightedRearDeltRaises">Weighted Rear Delt Raises </string>
    <string name="WeightedRearDeltRaisesDescription">The person will start belly down on an inclined bench. With dumbbells in each hand, the person will start with the
    dumbbells raised out in front of them with palms facing down and pull the arms backwards slightly past the persons side and then return back to the starting
    position</string>

    <string name="StandingOverheadWeightedPress">Standing Overhead Weighted Press</string>
    <string name="StandingOverheadWeightedPressDescription">The person will start in a standing position with the barbell on the shoulders and palms facing up. The person
    will then push the barbell over their heads fully extending their arms and then returning back to the starting position</string>


    Strings for Bicep Exercises
    <string name="DumbbellCurls">Dumbbell Curls</string>
    <string name="DumbbellCurlsDescription">To perform a dumbbell curl, the person will grab a dumbbell in one or both hands and curl the weight up to their shoulder and then
    return to a fully extended position either to the side or front of the person</string>

    <string name="MachineDumbbellCurls">Machine Dumbbell Curls</string>
    <string name="MachineDumbbellCurlsDescription">The person will go to a cable machine and attach a curl attachment of their choice. The machine height should be set close
    to the ground. When ready the person will stand in front of the machine grabbing the attachment with both hands and curl both arms at the same time to the users chest or
    shoulders and the return to the fully extended position</string>

    <string name="InclineDumbbellCurls">Incline Dumbbell Curls</string>
    <string name="InclineDumbbellCurlsDescription">The incline dumbbell curls is a variation of the dumbbell curl in which the person is seated in an inclined weight bench, making
    the arms go further back than a normal curl and lengthening the movement</string>

    <string name="SittingPreacherCurls">Sitting Preacher Curls</string>
    <string name="SittingPreacherCurlsDescription">The person will start in a seated position with a preacher curl bar gripped using both hands. They will then use both hands to curl
    the bar up to the chest/shoulder area and return back to the starting position with arms fully extended out</string>

    <string name="StrictPreacherCurls">Strict Preacher Curls</string>
    <string name="StrictPreacherCurlsDescription">The strict preacher curl is a variation of the preacher curl in which the person will stand with their back against a wall with
    a preacher curl bar and will perform the curls in this position. The wall will force the person to only use their arms and will not be able to use their body to help
    curl the weight up making this work strictly on the arms</string>


    Strings for Back Exercises
    <string name="BarbellDeadlift">Barbell Deadlift</string>
    <string name="BarbellDeadliftDescription">To perform the barbell deadlift, the person will start with the barbell on the ground at their feet in a standing position. The person will
    then bend over, making sure to keep their back straight, and grab the bar lifting it up until they are standing straight up. After reaching the peak they will then return back
    to the starting position on the floor</string>

    <string name="BarbellBentOverRow">Barbell Bent Over Row</string>
    <string name="BarbellBentOverRowDescription">The person will begin in the deadlift position and raise the bar off of the ground slightly being sure to keep the back straight,.
    They will then pull the bar up to their chest with their arms while remaining in this bent over position and then extending the arms back to the starting position. The person
    will continue this series of movements to complete this exercise</string>

    <string name="HexBarDeadlift">Hex Bar Deadlift</string>
    <string name="HexBarDeadliftDescription">The hex bar deadlift is a variation of the barbell deadlift in which the person will use a hex bar deadlift setup to complete their
    exercise. The person will stand in the middle of the hex bar and grab both handles on each side of the bar using these to pull the bar up until the person is standing
    straight up</string>

    <string name="OneArmDumbbellRow">One Arm Dumbbell Row</string>
    <string name="OneArmDumbbellRowDescription">The one arm dumbbell row is a variation of the bent over row in which the person will graba dumbbell in one hand at a time and get in
    the bent over position and use their arm to pull the dumbbell up to their chest then return back to the starting position with the arm fully locked out. The person will repeat
    this same movement on their alternate arm as well</string>

    <string name="PendlayRow">Pendlay Row</string>
    <string name="PendlayRowDescription">The pendlay row is yet another version of the bent over row except the person will start with the barbell on the floor before each rep. After
    the rep is reached on the peak, the person will return the barbell back to the floor each time</string>

    <string name="PullUps">Pull Ups</string>
    <string name="PullupsDescription">The pull up is performed on any pull up bar. The person will grab a hold of the bar and lift their feet off of the ground. They will then pull
    themselves up until their chin reaches the height of the bar then lower themselves back down until their arms are completely locked out</string>

    <string name="SeatedCableRow">Seated Cable Row</string>
    <string name="SeatedCableRowDescription">The seated cable row is similar to the barbell row but the user is seated in a cable row machine. The person will grab the handle and
    pull to their chest and return back to a fully extended position with their arms creating a "rowing" motion with their body</string>

    <string name="TBarRow">T Bar Row</string>
    <string name="TBarRowDescription">The t bar row is a variation of the barbell row in which on end of the barbell is attached in a landmine setup with the t bar attachment being
    connected to the other side. The person will grab this t bar attachment with both hands and pull the attachment to their chest and then return back to the starting position with arms
    fully extended out</string>


    Strings for Abdominal Exercises
    <string name="AbCrunchMachine">Ab Crunch Machine</string>
    <string name="AbCrunchMachineDescription">Ab Crunch Machine </string>

    <string name="AirBicycles">Air Bicycles</string>
    <string name="AirBicyclesDescription">Air Bicycles</string>

    <string name="Crunch">Crunch</string>
    <string name="CrunchDescription">Crunch</string>

    <string name="FlutterKick">Flutter Kick</string>
    <string name="FlutterKickDescription">Flutter Kick</string>

    <string name="LyingLegRaise">Lying Leg Raise</string>
    <string name="LyingLegRaiseDescription">Lying Leg Raise </string>

    <string name="Plank">Plank</string>
    <string name="PlankDescription">Plank</string>

    <string name="RussianTwist">Russian Twist</string>
    <string name="RussianTwistDescription">Russian Twist</string>

    <string name="VUp">V Up</string>
    <string name="VUpDescription">V Up</string>

    <string name="AbdominalRollout">Abdominal Rollout</string>
    <string name="AbdominalRolloutDescription">Abdominal Rollout</string>


    Strings for Glutes Exercises
    <string name="BarbbellHipThrust">Barbbell Hip Thrust</string>
    <string name="BarbellHipThrustDescription">Barbbell Hip Thrust </string>

    <string name="CableKickback">Cable Kickback</string>
    <string name="CableKickbackDescription">Cable Kickback</string>

    <string name="GluteBlaster">Glute Blaster</string>
    <string name="GluteBlasterDescription">Glute Blaster</string>

    <string name="GluteBridge">Glute Bridge</string>
    <string name="GluteBridgeDescription">Glute Bridge</string>

    <string name="MachineHipAbduction">Machine Hip Abduction</string>
    <string name="MachineHipAbductionDescription">Machine Hip Abduction</string>


    Strings for Hamstring Exercises
    <string name="StandingLunge">Standing Lunge</string>
    <string name="StandingLungeDescription">Standing Lunge </string>

    <string name="LegCurl">Leg Curl</string>
    <string name="LegCurlDescription">Leg Curl</string>

    <string name="RomanianDeadlift">Romanian Deadlift</string>
    <string name="RomanianDeadliftDescription">Romanian Deadlift</string>

    <string name="SeatedLegCurl">Seated Leg Curl</string>
    <string name="SeatedLegCurlDescription">Seated Leg Curl</string>

    <string name="ElevatedDeadlift">Elevated Deadlift</string>
    <string name="ElevatedDeadliftDescription">Elevated Deadlift</string>

    <string name="SingleLegHamstringCurl">Single Leg Hamstring Curl</string>
    <string name="SingleLegHamstringCurlDescription">Single Leg Hamstring Curl</string>


    Strings for Calves Exercises
    <string name="LegPressCalfRaise">Leg Press Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="LegPressCalfRaiseDescription">Leg Press Calf Raise</string>

    <string name="DonkeyCalfRaise">Donkey Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="DonkeyCalfRaiseDescription">Donkey Calf Raise</string>

    <string name="SeatedCalfRaise">Seated Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="SeatedCalfRaiseDescription">Seated Calf Raise</string>

    <string name="SmithMachineCalfRaise">Smith Machine Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="SmithMachineCalfRaiseDescription">Smith Machine Calf Raise</string>

    <string name="StandingBarbbellCalfRaise">Standing Barbbell Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="StandingBarbbellCalfRaiseDescription">Standing Barbbell Calf Raise</string>

    <string name="StandingDumbbellCalfRaise">Standing Dumbbell Calf Raise</string>
    <string name="StandingDumbbellCalfRaiseDescription">Standing Dumbbell Calf Raise</string>


    -- Strings for next and back buttons --
    <string name="BackButton">Previous Page</string>
    <string name="NextButton">Next Page</string>
    <string name="AddExercise">Add Exercise</string>


    -- Ignore this --
    -- Strings used in completed workouts activities --
    -- Strings that are used as workout titles -- -- Can also probably be deleted after data storage
    implementation
    <string name="CompletedWorkoutsTitle">Completed Workouts</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout01">Most Previous workout title goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout02">2nd Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout03">3rd Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout04">4th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout05">5th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout06">6th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout07">7th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout08">8th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout09">9th Most Previous workout goes here</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout10">10th Most Previous workout goes here</string>

    <string name="ViewCompletedWorkout">View Workout</string>

    -- Strings that are used in the workout descriptions -- -- can probably be deleted later on
    after implementation
    <string name="CompletedWorkout01Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 01 </string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout02Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 02</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout03Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 03</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout04Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 04</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout05Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 05</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout06Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 06</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout07Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 07</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout08Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 08</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout09Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 09</string>
    <string name="CompletedWorkout10Information">Workout time and exercise count goes here for workout 10 </string>


</resources>
